《邊橋謎案》前情提要
Previously on The Bridge...
包里裝的是什么
What's in the gym bag?
雷雷哥什么時候辜負過你
Has old Ray Ray ever let you down.
發射器
它們都指向了戴維·泰特
All roads lead back to David Tate.
調查局的戴維·泰特
David Tate? FBI?
你認識這個人
You know him?
戴維·泰特已經死了
David Tate's dead.
她當時打算離開戴維
She was gonna leave David.
我猜那晚他們有過爭吵
My guess is they got in a fighe that night,
之后她拽著凱萊布  去找她的新男人
she grabbed Caleb, went to be with her new man.
卻發生了意外
Never made it.
這到底是誰
Who the heck is this?
尸體的身份是
Body was I.D.'d
于八月六號失蹤的肯尼斯·黑斯廷
as Kenneth Hasting went missing in August 6.
馬可  這是肯尼斯·黑斯廷
Marco, this is Kenneth Hasting,
他的駕照還在使用中
and he has a current driver's license.
駕駛執照
這個人是戴維·泰特
That's David Tate.
你沒認出來我吧
You don't recognize me, do you?
我跟很多人打過交道
Look, I meet a lot of people...
你要干什么
Hey-hey... What the hell?
2007年2月10日  美洲邊境大橋上
There was hit-and-run on the Bridge of the Americas,
發生一起肇事逃逸
February 10, 2007.
你毀了我的人生
You took my whole life away.
我認識吉爾·泰特
I know Jill Tate.
我和她有外遇時  跟戴維還是朋友
We had an affair while I was friends with David.
她死于肇事逃逸時  你還在跟她交往嗎
Were you still with her when she died in the hit-and-run?
是的
Yes.
你就是橋那邊的那個人
You're the man across the bridge.
累了嗎
Tired?
沒有
Not really.
我也沒有
Me neither.
我兒子在哪里
Where is my son?
我兒子
My son?
僅供學習 禁止用于任何商業盈利行為
更多影視更新
請登陸www.YYeTs.com
翻譯
冰藍
胖兔純
愛卿遛小鳥
屯栗子
翻譯
爵士年代蓬蓬裙
lulu
foolyangyang
校對
wdjmhs
時間軸
愛卿遛小鳥
兜兜兜爹
萌
chance-coco
imok
No.Zero
后期  吉吉
總監  wdjmhs
邊橋謎案
第一季   第九集
馬可
Marco.
我已經和墨西哥城警方取得聯系
他們要答案
快了  隊長
我們知道他的長相
We know what he looks like.
厲害的美國專案組逮捕他了嗎
Has your fancy American task force arrested him yet?
還沒有
No, they haven't.
馬可
Marco,
在沙漠里殺掉印第安人是一回事
但他剛殺害的可是索爾先生的獨子
我明白  隊長
不  你不明白
如果你沒忙著跟蹤美國佬警探
你可能已經抓住他了
找到他  否則我們都會在監獄里刷馬桶
明白嗎
明白  隊長
他不會罷休的
He's not done.
我知道
I know.
華瑞茲的花花公子怎么卷進此事了
How does this Juarez playboy fit into this?
圣地亞哥·索爾是一起肇事逃逸事故的嫌疑犯
Santiago Sol was a suspect in the hit-and-run accident
事故導致泰特的妻子死在橋上
that killed Tate's wife on the bridge.
她說她愛我  而且
She told me she loved me, and...
想和我在一起
she wanted to be with me.
我不在乎她
It was nothing to me.
你在她身上泄欲
You used her for sex.
不是
No.
你愛過她嗎
You loved her?
當然不愛
No.
你早該告訴她
Well, you should've told her that.
她根本聽不進去
Oh, she believed what she wanted to believe.
那是因為你在騙她
That's 'cause you were lying to her.
真不敢相信  天啊
桑婭  并非所有事都是非黑即白的
Sonya, not everything is black and white.
如果他知道了呢
What if he knows.
不
No.
不可能
That's not possible.
我們是朋友
We were friends.
我和他一起出席他們的葬禮
I was at their funeral with him.
他毫不知情
He did not know.
如果他現在知道了呢
What if he knows now?
如果他現在知道了
What if he knows now
并放過了向你復仇的大好時機
and he didn't kill you when he had the chance...
因為他另有陰謀
because he's planning something else.
王八蛋  我的家人
我要回家
I'm going home.
凱撒
Cesar?
你好啊  你出來干什么
Hey, there. What are you doing out?
雷在哪
Where's Ray?
我不知道
I don't know.
從臉開始劃
Start with the face.
住手
凱撒  你干什么
雷在哪
在屋里
讓開
不  女士  拜托
別逼我做不想做的事
搞什么  你個混蛋
你裝什么爺們
你不過是個軟弱的仆人罷了
謝謝
Thank you.
我別無選擇
I had no choice.
現在怎么辦
What do we do now?
阿爾瑪  快接電話
她不接電話
She won't pick up.
你最近一次跟她說話是什么時候
When was the last time you spoke with her?
好幾天了
Days.
我有不詳的預感
I have a bad feeling.
格斯呢
What about Gus?
他也不接電話
Oh, he's not picking up either.
潔娜  你嚇我一跳
Zina, hi. You scared me.
怎么了
Something wrong?
沒事  只是...
No, you-you just...
就是...
Well, yeah, it's just-just...
你不是說你還在...  還沒回來
I thought you said you were still in, uh, out of town
所以要遲些見面嗎
and that's why we couldn't meet until later?
你說你還在拉雷多
You said you were stil in Laredo.
-我說過嗎  -是啊
- I did? - Yeah.
你是在耍我嗎
Are you messing with me?
我還留著你的短信
I-I have the text.
這不是我發的  格斯
Um, that's not me, Gus.
這是我以前的手機號
That's my old cell number.
我搬家之后我們就沒發過短信了
We haven't texted since I moved.
希望你沒給這妹子透露太多
Hopefully, you didn't tell this girl too much.
等下
Wait, so..
我們稍后不約會嗎
we are not meeting later?
不啊
Um, no.
好吧
Okay, uh...
我得走了
I... I have to go.
阿爾瑪
Alma?!
阿爾瑪  孩子們
Alma?! Girls?!
也許她們出去了
Maybe they're out.
這個時間
At this hour?
會去哪
Where would they be?
羅薩里奧
Rosario...
我是馬可
索菲亞和莉莉跟你在一起嗎
好吧
我知道了  什么時候
她說要去哪了嗎
好的  不不不
Okay. No, no, no, no.
沒什么事
謝謝  再見
她們和阿爾瑪在一起
They're with Alma.
她一小時前把她們接走了
She picked them up an hour ago.
那就好
That's good.
每晚睡在同一個人身邊很難嗎
Is it hard to sleep next to the same person every night?
別現在提這茬啊  桑婭
Not now, Sonya.
我在找阿爾瑪和孩子們呢
I'm trying to find Alma and my kids, all right?
我需要你幫忙
I need your help.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
跟我說說戴維·泰特
Tell me about David Tate.
他...
Oh, he..
想做出些改變
he wanted to make a difference.
一直想立案調查華瑞茲那些女孩的死
Kept trying to open an investigation on the Dead girls of Juarez.
然后呢
What happened?
他的上司不允許我們調查
His bosses shut us down.
他工作出色嗎
Was he good at his job?
非常出色
Very.
意外發生之后
By then, the accident happened
他整個人都變了
and he's changed.
所以他干這個應該很在行
So he's gonna be good at this.
你什么意思
What-what does that mean?
無論他下一步計劃是什么  都不會出錯
Whatever he' planning next, he won' make mistakes.
你非得現在說這樣的話嗎
Did you really hav to say that right now?
實事求是
It's the truth.
問題就在這里  桑婭
that is the problem, Sonya!
你為什么不能說點別人愛聽的話呢
Why can't you just tell people what they want to hear.
你愛聽什么話
What do you want to hear?
我愛聽你說我家人不會有事
I want to hear my family's gonna be okay.
我現在得讓自己有信心
I really need to believe that right now
好的  好的
Okay, okay.
是我妻子
It's her.
阿爾瑪
Alma.
你好  馬可
Hello, Marco
好久不見
It's been a long time.
我家人在哪
Where is my family?
你有一個美滿的家庭  馬可
You have a beautiful family, Marco.
很難想象你居然身在福中不知福
It's hard to imagine why a man would just throw that away.
狗娘養的
Son of a bitch.
我要宰了你
I'm... I'm gonna kill you.
也許你有這個機會
Well, maybe you'll get that chance.
她們在哪
Where are they?
跟我在一起
With me.
誰想玩游戲
Who wants to have some fun?
沒事吧
Is everything okay?
沒事  公事而已
Oh, yeah, it was just work.
你真不想給你丈夫打電話
You sure you don't want to call your husband
告訴他你們在哪嗎
and let him know where you are?
不想
No.
我給你買了這個
I got you this..
還有這個
..And this.
你太美了
You look beautiful.
狗娘養的
傻逼
她們在他手上
He has them!
你千里迢迢就是來看她干活的嗎
Did you come all this way to watch her work?
不是
No.
換我就會
I would.
你怎么想的  斯蒂文
What's on your mind, Steven?
我的跟你談談
I need to talk to you.
好的
Okay.
我發現工作對口齒有幫助
I find that work helps the tongue.
你來試試
Give it a shot.
沒錯
Yeah.
確實感覺很好
Yeah, that feels good.
你有心事嗎
What's on your mind?
我殺了一個人
I killed a man.
好吧
Okay.
你會說我犯戒了嗎
Are you gonna tell me I sinned?
得看當時的情形
Depends on the situation.
你我都清楚
As we both know,
犯戒這種事是對有信仰的人講的
sinning supposes a belief in a higher power.
而你不信神  斯蒂文
Which you lack, Steven?
我信
Yes, I do.
被你殺死的人
This man you killed,
他是好人還是壞人
was he a good man or was he a bad man?
他身上有這個
He carried this.
這好像是...  皮膚
Well, that looks like... That's skin
人皮
That's human skin.
這人是誰
Who was this man?
他是伊娃的男友
He was Eva's boyfriend.
赫克托
Hector?
她跟我提起過他
She's told me about him.
尸體在哪
Where's the body?
我拖到沙漠里  準備埋掉
I took it out to the desert to bury it...
但發生了一件怪事
and the funniest thing happened.
有人過來把尸體搶走了
This man came and took it from me.
這是好事
Well, that's a good thing.
你就會說這些話嗎
Well, that's-that's all you're gonna say.
你如釋重負了吧  斯蒂文
I think you're I the clear, Steven.
我該怎么對伊娃講
What do I tell Eva?
實話實說
The truth.
她是個好女人
Oh, she's a good woman.
沒錯  她很特別
Yes, she is. Special.
沒錯
That's right.
鮑勃  我一直對她有非分之想
Bob, I've been thinking about her in a special way.
這很正常  斯蒂文
That's natural, Steven.
咱們去吃火腿沙拉  邊吃邊聊
Let's discuss this over a ham salad.
很高興聽你這么說
I'm so glad you said that.
最近食欲很好
I've been so hungry of late.
經歷這種事后會這樣的
That happens after such things.
我第一次殺人后總是吃不夠芝士漢堡
My first kill, I couldn' get enough cheeseburgers.
我以前經常和家人來這里
I used to come here with my family.
你兒子叫什么名字
What was your son's name?
迦勒
Caleb.
他總喜歡把石子放在滑梯上
He used to put rocks on that slide.
他就喜歡玩這個
That was his thing, you know.
還有樂高積木
That and Legos.
總讓他無比的開心
Made him totally happy.
他是怎么出事的
How did it happen?
一次交通事故
A car accident.
我們沒必要談這個
We don't have to talk about this.
沒事的
Oh, it's okay.
講出來舒服多了
Feels good to talk about it.
尤其是對你
Especially with you.
這件事讓我變了一個人
It made me a different person.
我對世界充滿了怨恨
I-I was mad... at the world.
當我在街上看見幸福美滿的家庭時
I'd see happy families on the street and...
我會希望厄運降臨在他們身上
I'd wish bad things on them.
這感覺一定很糟
That must be terrible.
我心中仍有那憤怒
I still have that anger.
我天天都在控制它
Work on it every day.
我無法想象這樣失去自己的孩子
I can't imagine losing a child like that.
希望你永遠也不用體會
I hope you never do.
是啊
Yeah.
我們帶孩子們去吃點東西  然后
Let's get the girls something to eat, and, uh,
我會給你一個驚喜
I'll show you the surprise.
好吧
Okay.
格斯
Gus!
真慶幸你沒事
我打電話你一定要接  知道嗎
每次都要接知道嗎  每次都要
Okay? You always pick it up! Always.
知道了  發生什么事了
Okay. What is wrong?
阿爾瑪和妹妹們呢
Where is Alma and the girls?
我們不知道
We don't know.
格斯  你認識一個叫肯尼斯·黑斯廷的人嗎
Gus, do you know a person named Kenneth Hasting?
黑斯廷先生
Mr. Hasting?
你是說阿爾瑪的同事
The guy who works with Alma?
你說什么
What?
他們是大學同事
At the university.
為什么你會問起他
Why are you asking about him?
聽我說
Okay, listen to me.
告訴我阿爾瑪說過要離開嗎
I need to know if Alma said anything about leaving.
沒有
No.
索菲亞和莉莉呢
And Sophia and Lilly?
我以為你們已經抓到兇手了
I thought you said you had the guy.
我們錯了
We were wrong.
我是桑婭·克羅斯
Sonya Cross.
肯尼斯來過家里嗎
Has Kenneth been in my house?
我不清楚
I-I don't know.
可能吧
Maybe.
你應該早告訴我的  格斯
You should have told me that, Gus
我知道  只是
I know, it's..
她叫我不要告訴你
She asked me not to.
你確定是同一個人嗎
Are you sure it's the same guy?
是的
Yes.
她們不會出事吧
Are they going to be okay?
我不知道
I don't know.
他們找到黑斯廷的公寓了
They found Hasting's apartment.
我得把你帶去警局
Okay. I'm taking you to the station.
你待在這里不安全
It's not safe for you here, alright?
快走
Let's go.
他在整棟樓都埋了炸藥
He had this entire building wired to blow.
有他的蹤跡嗎
Any sign of him?
還沒有
Nothing yet.
聽著  我們會抓到他
Listen, we're gonna get this guy,
我們會把你的妻子和孩子們救回來的
and we're gonna get your wife and kids back.
這家伙還真閑啊
This guy had a lot of free time on his hands.
有什么發現嗎
What you got?
你親自看看吧
See for yourself.
小心腳下
Watch your step.
這就是你說的驚喜嗎
Is this the surprise?
不  我忙活這個好一陣子了
No, I've been working on this for a long time.
這曾經是個狩獵小屋
Used to be an old hunting cabin.
你絕對想象不到我做了些什么
You're not gonna believe what I've done.
這里面有兩只倉鼠  誰想先來喂它們
I got two hamsters. Who wants to feed 'em first?
進來吧
Come on.
你來嗎
You coming?
好
Yeah.
快來吧
Come on.
好了
Okay.
不許偷看
No peeking.
好的
Okay.
快看  媽媽
親愛的  我看不到
這就好了
Here we go.
不許偷看
No peeking.
好的
Okay.
你保證
Promise?
我保證
I promise.
姑娘們  告訴媽媽把眼睛閉上
Girls, tell your mommy to keep her eyes shut.
這是一個大大的驚喜
This is a very big surprise.
我真的不想再玩這個游戲了
I really don't want to play this game anymore.
你會嚇到孩子們的
You're scaring the girls.
快了
Almost.
把手伸出來
Hold out your hand.
好了
Okay.
現在用力握住這個
Now, hold on to this very tight.
睜開雙眼
Open your eyes.
天啊
Oh, God.
現在要小心了
Now, careful.
如果你的手離開那個手柄你就只剩五秒鐘
Take your hand off that lever, you only have five seconds
和你的女兒們說再見了
to say good-bye to your daughters.
驚喜
Surprise.
上帝啊
Oh, God.
不不不
No, no, no, no, no.
等等
Stop!
你在做什么
What are you doing?!
怎么了  媽媽
What's wrong, Mommy.
打開門
Open the door.
肯尼斯
Kenneth!
你在做什么
What are you doing?
門  把門打開
The door-- open the door!
把門打開
Open the door!
Open the door.
別走  別走
Don't go. Don't go.
別走
Don't go.
打開  別把我們留在這里
Open! Don't leave us here!
肯尼斯
Kenneth.
別走  別走
Don't go! Don't go.
天啊
Oh, God.
謊言就像小小的黑色蝴蝶  史蒂文
Lies are like little black butterflies, Steven.
它們依附著你  直到你說出真相
They cling to you till you speak the truth...
然后給它們自由
And you set them free.
伊娃  史蒂文有話想對你說
Eva, Steven has something he'd like to tell you.
你好
Hi.
你好  伊娃
Hello, Eva.
鮑勃  我們能單獨談談嗎
Uh, Bob, can we have a minute, please
當然
Of course.
最近過得怎么樣
How you doing?
還好
Okay.
聽著  我需要
Listen, I-I nee to..
告訴你些事情
tell you something.
什么事
Yes?
赫克托死了
Hector's dead.
怎么死的
How?
他在我家襲擊我
He attacked me in my home,
我別無選擇
and I didn't have choice.
你愛他
You loved him.
我不該
I shouldn't have.
對不起  伊娃
I'm sorry, Eva.
考珀正在查華瑞茲那邊所有的資料
Copper's going through everything in Juarez.
他極其小心
He was meticulous.
肯定在那
It's got to be in there.
爸爸
Dad.
怎么了  格斯
What is it, Gus?
你找到他們了嗎
Did you find them?
不  還沒有
No, not yet.
我們現在非常忙  好嗎
I mean, look, we're busy right now, all right?
我知道  但是等一下好嗎
I know, but just wait, okay?
你記起有關肯尼斯的事了
Did you remember something about Kenneth?
不  是關于潔娜的
No, it-it's about Zina.
潔娜
Z-Zina?
現在不是時候  格斯
現在不行
N-Not now.
爸爸  這很重要
Dad, it's important, okay?!
是什么事  孩子
What is it, son?
我一直在給潔娜發短信  但
I've been texting Zina this whole time, but...
但其實不是她
but it wasn't her.
"不是她"是什么意思
What do you mean "It wasn't her"?
我今早碰到她  她對短信的事一無所知
I ran into her this morning, but she didn't know anything.
也就是說  我把案件有關的詳情
And so whoever I was texting
告訴了冒名短信我的人
I told them things about the case
因為他們說對案子很感興趣
because they said they were interested.
給我看下
Let me see.
提到我不少次
You write a lot about me.
我知道  很抱歉
I know. I-I'm sorry.
性感婦人
"Milf"
Mother I'd like to fuck  縮寫
指豐滿  有吸引力  將近30歲的女人
就是
I-It's a mom I..
我知道是什么意思
I know what it means.
但我沒孩子啊
I don't have children.
桑婭  拜托
Sonya, please.
-快點  -要專注
- Come on. - Focus
她最后一次聯系你是什么時候
When's the last time she contacted you?
幾周前
A couple of weeks ago.
跟她說過吉娜被拘留的事嗎
Did you text anything about Gina being in custody?
說了
Yeah.
她因我而死的
It's my fault she's dead.
不  不
No, no, no.
你不知道
You didn't know.
你不可能知道
You couldn't have known.
是他
It's him.
她不知道這孩子今天遇到真的潔娜了
He doesn't know that he ran into the real Zina this morning.
給他發短信  說你想和他見面
You know what, tex him, say you want to meet.
快點
Go on.
讓我來
Let me, let me.
好了
Okay.
快點  快點  快點  快點
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
搞定
It's on.
漢克  我們走
Come on, Hank, let's go.
招待  過來一下
Excuse me?
怎么了
Yeah.
幫我把這張紙交給坐在長凳上的那個人
I need you to give this to the man sitting on tha bench.
多謝
Thank you.
他遲到了
He's late.
過來了
Incoming.
等等  別急
Hey, hey, hang on, hang on.
有人讓我把這個交給你
Somebody told me to give this to you.
別動
Hey, hold it.
你在干什么  孩子
What are you doing, son?
-有人讓我把這個給你  -他在哪
- A man told me to give that to you. - Where?
他在那
He's over there.
這是什么
What is it?
GPS坐標
走吧
Let's go.
寶貝兒
把你妹妹帶到角落里去
動作要快
老天  幫幫我
Oh, God, help me.
別讓我女兒死
聽到我父親的消息嗎
Have you heard from my dad?
沒有
No.
我很擔心
I'm worried.
我知道  一有動靜我會通知你的
I know. I'll let you know if we hear anything.
那是吉娜吧
So that is Gina?
是啊
Yes.
我不知道原來我在跟他說話
I didn't know I wa talking to him.
他很狡猾
He's smart.
他計劃這一切很久了
He's been planning this for long time.
奇怪的是
What's weird is...
他卻讓我離父親更近了
He made me closer to my dad.
格斯  你在說什么
What are you talking about, Gus?
我們聊天的時候
When we were chatting.
你以為自己再和一個女孩子聊天
You thought you were talking to a girl.
但我對他傾訴對父親的感情時
I know, but he gave good advice,
他給我很多很好的建議
when I told him how I was feeling about my father.
格斯
Gus...
我還在忙
I have work to do.
嗯  好
Yeah.
不打擾你了
Sure.
應該在那邊
Should be down there.
馬可  你得做好準備
Gonna have this rigged, Marco.
可能是陷阱
Could be rigged.
馬可  別激動
Marco, easy!
慢點  慢點
Go easy, easy, easy!
阿爾瑪  阿爾瑪
Alma! Alma!
孩子們和你在一起嗎
孩子們都在這里
只有你們在里面嗎
是的
用什么東西把這個砸開
I need something to break this down.
閃開點
Look out.
行了
馬可
Marco
這是個手雷
小心  小心
孩子們
快和我出來
快點  孩子們
來吧  快走  快走
Come on, go, go, go.
快跑  快跑
Run, run, run, run, run!
救救我
把手給我
小心  小心
沒事的  有我呢
有我在
別害怕  有我在
I have you.
看著我
別害怕
我們要配合好
我數三個數
你把它給我
我扔的時候  你就趕快蹲下  明白嗎
一
二
三
沒事了
都過去了
我想回家
我帶你回家
他們沒事了  你爸爸找到她們了
Hey, they are OK, your father has them.
-他們捉住他了嗎  -沒有
- Did they get him? - No.
我想回家
I want to go home.
不行  我開車送你去安全房
You can't. I'm driving you to a safe house.
你爸爸在那和你碰面  走吧
Your father will meet you there. Let's go.
挖得夠深了
That's probably deep enough.
謝謝
你要告訴雷嗎
You are gonna tell Ray.
你說呢
Should I?
我覺得還是別告訴他了
I don't think it's a good idea.
等等
Wait.
我來
Let me.
然后會怎樣
What happens next?
倒上石灰
Lime.
加速腐爛
It will speed up the decomposition.
尸體一個星期之內就會消失
The bodies will be gone in a week.
不  我的意思是然后我們怎么辦
No, I mean wha happens next?
說不準
Ah, it depends.
希望能風平浪靜
Hopefully, nothing.
我得帶我老婆出去看場電影
I'm gonna take my wife out to go see a movie.
假裝什么也沒發生
and pretend none of this happened.
謝謝你  凱撒
Thank you, Cesar.
你救了我的命
You saved my life.
沒什么  夫人
我們明天再談吧
We'll talk tomorrow.
有關地道的事
About the tunnel.
到底該怎么辦
How it's gonna work now.
我們知道他是誰
We know who he is.
我們會抓住他的
We'll get him.
所以這一切都是因為我爸
So this is all about m Dad?
我沒這么說
I didn't say that.
他做了什么事
What did he do?
你該去問他
You should ask him that.
為什么黑斯廷要這么做
Why would Mr. Hasting do this?
沒道理啊
It doesn't make sense.
他還有什么事沒做
What he's not done?
不太對勁兒
It doesn't make sense.
怎么了
What?